John and Ginny Dildine collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Sound Recordings
  - AFC 1975/001: SR037 (2), Recorded: unknown, RXG 0728; 30:16
    17:48 The announcer identifies the previous selection and the next selection
    18:05 Musical performance from [?]
    22:20 Musical performance from [?]
    23:33 Musical performance from Mexico
    26:43 Musical performance from [?]
    28:00 The announcer closes the broadcast
    28:12 Musical performance [closing theme]
    30:16 End of recording
    30:16 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR038 (1), Recorded: unknown, RXG 0729; 56:03
    This is not a recording of a Dildine program. Rather, it is the recording for a radio broadcast called "The R&B Special" on station WDON, Montgomery County, MD. The DJ's name is Mike Pufford.
    Start The DJ, Mike [Pufford], says the prior song was "Tiger Lily" by the Five Keys.
    0:32 "Johnny's House Party" Jimmie Beasley
    3:28 Commercial break for Schlitz beer.
    4:06 "The Bad Motorcycle" Story Sisters
    5:58 Commercial break for Shop Silver Spring Day Sale
    6:49 "Roll Over Beethoven" Chuck Berry
    9:07 DJ talking about the program.
    9:55 "Dream On" The Five Keys
    12:22 Station break for WDON
    12:50 "Fall guy" Titus Turner
    14:48 Commercial break for the Suburban Beauty School.
    16:38 "Wham Bam" Googy [Rene]
    18:53 "Hello Little Girl" Lloyd Price
    20:48 The DJ talks about the 2 previous songs and the next song.
    21:13 "Ain't That Love" Ray Charles
    24:00 Thank you to the companies who donated the records for the program.
    24:24 "Leave My Kids Alone" Little Willie John
    26:50 Station break for WDON
    27:50 "Been So Long" The Pastels
    30:21 The DJ talks about the previous song and the next song.
    30:46 "King of Fools" Sam Hawkins
    32:51 Commercial break for Shop Silver Spring Day Sale
    33:55 "Beside My Love" The Doves
    36:05 The DJ talks about the previous song and the next song.
    36:27 "Try the Impossible" Lee Andrews and the Harps
    39:28 Station break for WDON
    40:41 "Stormy Weather" The Leaders
    43:33 DJ talks about the music he plays. Station break for WDON
    44:18 "Who's That Knockin'" The Genies
    46:26 Commercial break for Shop Silver Spring Day Sale
    47:43 "I Do the Shimmy Shimmy" Bobby Freeman
    50:35 "So Long" Fats Domino
    52:38 Thank you to the companies who donated the records for the program.
    53:03 ["All Night Long"]
    53:35 DJ closes the broadcast with the record playing in the background.
    56:03 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR038 (2), Recorded: ca. 1960 [Eisenhower was still President], RXG 0729; 53:20
    This is a recording for a John Dildine radio broadcast. For the first 16 minutes, or so, he plays a phonograph record by Lead Belly (Huddie Ledbetter). The rest of the broadcast features Dave Sear, live in the studio.
    Start "Railroad Bill"- Dildine introduces the program and plays a phonograph record by Lead Belly.
    1:30 "Boll Weevil" Lead Belly
    4:55 "Boogie Woogie" Lead Belly
    7:58 "Good Morning Blues" Lead Belly
    10:50 Dildine does a station break.
    12:40 "Every Time I Feel the Spirit" Lead Belly
    13:56 "Swing Low Sweet Chariot" Lead Belly
    14:45 "They Hung Him on a Cross" Lead Belly
    16:42 Dildine talks about the Leadbelly record. He introduces Dave Sear. Sear performs mostly Lead Belly songs.
    17:25 "Poor Howard" Sear with banjo
    19:52 "Dhrinnin Dru Drinnin" Sear with guitar [The first line is: "'Tis a mournful sad ditty I'll tell you right now"]
    22:10 "Kisses Sweeter Than Wine" Sear with guitar
    25:45 Dildine does a station break.
    26:23 The Song of the Ox Driver" Sear with banjo
    31:38 "Dunderbeck's Machine" Sear with banjo
    33:30 "Ha Ha this A-Way" Sear with banjo
    36:45 "Almost Day" Sear with banjo [This song is also known as "Christmas is Coming" and "Chickens Crowing for Midnight"]
    37:35 "I'm Almost Done" Sear with banjo [this song is also know as "On Monday I was Arrested"]
    40:37 Dildine does a station break.
    41:53 "Roll on, Columbia, Roll On" Sear with banjo [This is a Woody Guthrie song.]
    46:38 "John Henry" Sear with banjo
    51:04 Dildine closes the broadcast.
    53:20 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR039, Recorded: 1961-02-08, RAA 54525; 14:31
    Donal Leace recorded. Leace sings and plays guitar on all songs.
    Start John Dildine introduces this radio broadcast. He says that he will play a tape of Donal Lease.
    0:38 "If I'd Known"
    3:56 "Joshua"
    6:36 "Old Blue"
    11:09 "On My Way"
  - AFC 1975/001: SR040, Recorded: 1961-02-08, RXG 0730; 14:23
    This is a recording for a John Dildine radio broadcast.
    Start John Dildine introduces the program and Donal Leace.
    0:35 "If I'd Known" Leace
    3:53 "Joshua Fit the Battle of Jericho" Leace
    6:30 "Old Blue" Leace
    11:00 "On My Way" Leace
  - AFC 1975/001: SR041, Recorded: 1961-03-18, RXG 0731; 32:01
    This is the first of three parts of a concert by Tom Paley, John Cohen and Mike Seeger. The other two parts are SR042 and SR043. The concert took place in Washington, D.C.
    Start "Up Jumped the Devil" Cohen, Paley and Seeger (instrumental)
    1:30 Introduction of Paley and Cohen by Seeger. Seeger introduces himself. Talking.
    3:40 "Battleship of Maine" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    6:55 Talking about the songs and where they learned them.
    8:35 "Down in the Willow Garden" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    11:13 Talking about the early days of the music they play. Talk about the instruments they play.
    13:30 "Fly Around My Pretty Little Miss" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    16:10 Talking about the next song.
    17:15 "Will the Weaver" [Seeger prefers to call this song "Everyday Dirt] Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    19:45 Introduction of the next song.
    21:23 "Cuckoo" John Cohen
    24:00 Introduction of the next song.
    25:45 "Sail Away Ladies" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    27:48 Introduction of the next three songs. [Only one song is recorded on this tape. The rest are on SR042.]
    29:05 "FDR is Back Again" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
  - AFC 1975/001: SR042, Recorded: 1961-03-08, RXG 0732; 31:21
    This is the second of three parts of a concert by Tom Paley, John Cohen and Mike Seeger. The other two parts are SR041 and SR043. The concert took place in Washington, D.C.
    Start Introduction of the next song. Discussion of banjo tuning.
    2:23 "Now He's Gone, I'm Glad He's Gone" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    5:30 Introduction of the next song. Discussion of the venue for this night's concert.
    7:45 "The Democratic Donkey" Cohen, Paley (lead vocal) and Seeger
    11:25 "Lost All My Money But a Two Dollar Bill" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    14:15 Introduction of the next song. "Selling their records," which are available $3.25 for 10 inch and $4.00 for 12 inch.
    17:20 "Hold the Woodpile Down" Cohen (lead vocal), Paley and Seeger
    20:40 Return from intermission.
    21:05 "Black Mountain Rag" Cohen, Paley and Seeger (instrumental)
    22:48 Introduction of the next song.
    23:30 "I'll Roll In My Sweet Baby's Arms" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    26:35 Introduction of the next song. Talking about Howard Johnson restaurants.
    28:05 "The All Go Hungry Hash House" Cohen (lead vocal), Paley and Seeger
  - AFC 1975/001: SR043, Recorded: 1961-03-08, RXG 0733; 29:21
    This is the third of three parts of a concert by Tom Paley, John Cohen and Mike Seeger. The other two parts are SR041 and SR042. The concert took place in Washington, D.C.
    Start Introduction of the next song. Discussion of the autoharp.
    0:57 "When First Unto this Country" Mike Seeger, vocal and autoharp
    3:42 Introduction of the next song. One of the band members dedicated the song to "all the single men in the audience."
    5:16 "The Man Who Wrote Home Sweet Home Never Was a Married Man" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    8:25 Introduction of the next song. They call it "Leaving Home" but it is usually called "Frankie and Johnny."
    9:55 "Leaving Home" Cohen, Paley and Seeger
    13:11 John Dildine is introduced as recording this concert and the person who first broadcast the trio [which became The New Lost City Ramblers]. The next song is dedicated to Dildine.
    15:20 "Old Molly Hare" Cohen, Paley and Mike Seeger [lead vocal and fiddle]
    17:38 Introduction of the next song. At one point it is called "The Railroad Blues" and a bit later it is called "The Freight Train Blues."
    18:30 "The Railroad Blues" Tom Paley, vocal and guitar
    21:30 Introduction of the next song.
    22:06 "Hot corn" John Cohen, lead vocal and mandolin, Paley and Seeger
    24:51 Introduction of the next song.
    25:45 "Take a Drink on Me" Cohen, Paley, lead vocal, and Seeger
    29:21 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR044 - PART 1 OF 2, Recorded: 1961-04-28, RXG 0734; 48:02
    This is the first half of a tape which is a potpourri of several musicians all recorded by an unidentified HOST. Many of the recordings, but not all, were done at the Laughing Buddha club, which may have been located on the West Coast. This tape itself seems to have been recorded by John Dildine.
    Start Bagpipes George Armstrong
    1:48 "The Back of Bennachie" Gerry Armstrong
    5:20 The unidentified HOST talks about the guitar Gerry Armstrong played on the previous song.
    7:05 "Ground Hog" George and Gerry Armstrong [guitar and lap dulcimer]
    10:08 The HOST introduces the next song.
    10:45 George Armstrong introduces Bob Beers and a "dancing puppet" [called a limber jack].
    11:55 Fiddle tunes Bob Beers [fiddle] and one of the Armstrongs on the "limber jack"
    12:55 George Armstrong shows and demonstrates a corn stalk fiddle. He introduces the next song as a corn stalk and dulcimer concerto.
    13:45 "Corn Stalk Fiddle" George and Gerry Armstrong [corn stalk fiddle and dulcimer]
    14:50 The HOST talks about the previous few songs and the show at the Laughing Buddha.
    15:50 George Armstrong introduces the double or courting dulcimer. It was made by Howie Mitchell of Lexington, VA. The HOST called the instrument "twicimer."
    16:40 "Little Moses" George and Gerry Armstrong [double dulcimer]
    19:30 The HOST closes the Armstrong portion of this tape. He then introduces Judy Collins [recorded].
    20:55 "John Riley" Judy Collins
    24:45 The HOST talks about the similarity between Judy Collins and Don Crawford.
    25:48 "Tim Evans" Judy Collins [Ms. Collins says this song was written by Ewan McColl]
    29:15 The HOST talks about Christy, the man who actually murdered Tim Evens' wife and child.
    31:12 "Black is the Color" Judy Collins
    34:13 The Host talks about Judy Collins' guitar playing and a record she recently released, "A Maid of Constant Sorrow." He talks about a performer named Bob Grossman. He talks about the Laughing Buddha club. He talks about Pete Stanley. The HOST says he recorded Collins and the Armstrongs at the Laughing Buddha club. He says he recorded Pete Stanley in the front hall of his house. He talks about a 12 string guitar Stanley plays.
    45:24 "San Francisco Bay Blues" Pete Stanley [12 string guitar and vocal]
    48:02 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR044 - PART 2 OF 2, Recorded: 1961-04-28, RXG 0734; 48:02
    This is the second half of a tape which is a potpourri of several musicians all recorded by an unidentified HOST. Many of the recordings, but not all, were done at the Laughing Buddha club, which may have been located on the West Coast. This tape itself seems to have been recorded by John Dildine.
    Start The host talks about several performers, where they are performing and a bit about their private lives.
    5:10 "Number 9" [may also be known as "Dark Was the Night"] Pete Stanley
    7:38 "He Was a Friend of Mine" Pete Stanley
    11:22 The Host says he will finish up Pete Stanley by playing an instrumental medley.
    11:48 "Flop Eared mule," "Old Joe Clark" and "Cripple Creek" Pete Stanley
    13:30 The host talks bout the performers at the Laughing Buddha in July and August. He talks is detail about how he recorded and mixed some of Don Crawford's performances.
    16:45 "Hootchie Kootchie Man" Don Crawford
    19:51 The HOST talks about the previous song.
    20:20 "Kilgary Mountain" Don Crawford
    26:30 "The Ballad of the Springhill Mine Disaster" [Crawford says that this song was written by Ewan McColl and Peggy Seeger and that he learned it from them.] Don Crawford
    31:36 Don Crawford tells a story about Leadbelly and plays bits of "Goodnight Irene" and "Ha-Ha This Away."
    34:43 Medley of "Good Morning Captain, Good Morning Son" and "My Jerry Was and Arkansas Mule" Don Crawford
    38:10 The Ballad of Tim Evans" Don Crawford
    43:52 The host talks about Don Crawford.
    48:12 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR045, Recorded: 1961-05-15, RAA 54526; 27:23
    This is one part of a concert with Howie Mitchell, Charlotte (Char) Daniels and Donal Leace. Other parts are on SR046 and SR047.
    Start "Passing Through" Daniels
    3:07 Mitchell introduces the concert and says it is the 5th Annual.
    6:07 The first line of this song is "I'll sing you a song, It's not very long," the title may be "The Lazy Farmer" Mitchell
    8:10 Mitchell talks about the music to be performed in this concert. He introduces Donal Leace.
    9:12 "Joshua Fit (sic) the Battle of Jericho" Leace
    12:32 Leace talking. He's employed by the US Senate. He talks about Senators Eastland and Fong.
    15:25 "All the Pretty little Horses" Leace
    18:22 "John Henry" Leace
    21:40 "Old Blue" Leace
    27:23 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR046, Recorded: 1961-05-15, RAA 54527; 26:22
    This is one part of a concert with Howie Mitchell, Charlotte (Char) Daniels and Donal Leace. Other parts are on SR045 and SR047.
    Start Mitchell introduces the next song
    1:56 "Two Sisters" Mitchell, mountain dulcimer
    3:56 Mitchell talks about and demonstrates the autoharp. He introduces the next song.
    7:07 [unidentified song about "Old Baggins?"] Mitchell, autoharp
    9:56 [unidentified song] Mitchell, guitar
    12:30 "Lady Day" Mitchell, banjo
    17:42 Mitchell discusses and demonstrates the mountain dulcimer.
    19:46 [unidentified song about pigs and true love] Mitchell, mountain dulcimer
    22:25 "Speak to Me Only with thine Eyes" Mitchell, guitar
    26:06 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR047, Recorded: 1961-05-15, RAA 54528; 13:41
    This is the final part of a concert with Howie Mitchell, Charlotte (Char) Daniels and Donal Leace. Other parts are on SR045 and SR046.
    Start Donal Leace is introduced.
    0:30 "The Virgin Mary Had a Baby Boy" Leace and others
    4:35 "Amen" Leace and others
    6:47 [unidentified song] Leace and others
    9:58 "This Old Town Too Long" Leace and others
    13:41 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR048, Recorded: 1961-05-05, RXG 0735; 27:41
    This is the first of four parts of the Columbia Heights Boys Club 5th Annual Concert. No details of the concert are given. The recording quality is ok, but with an echo or distortion of some sort.
    Start Noise
    0:30 Passing Through" Char [Charlotte] Daniels
    3:25 Daniels introduces Howie Mitchell. Mitchell introduces the concert and talks a bit about the songs. [He does not say specifically what the concert is, who sponsors it, etc.]
    6:35 "Young Man Wouldn't Hoe Corn" Mitchell [a cappella]
    8:27 Howie Mitchell talks about the songs. He introduces Donal Leace.
    9:39 "Joshua" Leace
    12:50 Leace talks about his job with the US Senate.
    16:06 "All the Pretty Little horses" Leace
    18:38 "John Henry" Leace
    21:58 "Old Blue" Leace
    27:41 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR049, Recorded: 1961-05-05, RXG 0736; 22:17
    This is the second of four parts of the Columbia Heights Boys Club 5th Annual Concert. No details of the concert are given. The recording quality is ok, but with an echo or distortion of some sort.
    Start "Pastures of Plenty" Char [Charlotte] Daniels
    3:12 Daniels talks about Woody Guthrie. She introduces the next song.
    3:57 "Dry Bed" Daniels
    5:20 "Old Maid's Lament" Daniels
    9:15 Daniels introduces the next song. She says it is a recipe for moonshine.
    9:58 "Copper kettle" Daniels
    13:48 "Virgin Mary" Daniels
    17:45 "Frankie and Johnny" Daniels
    22:17 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR050, Recorded: 1961-05-05, RXG 0737; 15:10
    This is the third of four parts of the Columbia Heights Boys Club 5th Annual Concert. No details of the concert are given. The recording quality is ok, but with an echo or distortion of some sort.
    Start Audience noise only
    0:35 Howie Mitchell introduces the next song. It is a story about King Henry who ate string.
    1:54 "Henry King" Mitchell
    3:58 Mitchell introduces the next song.
    4:25 "The Cruel Mother" [also known as "Greenwood Sidey"] Mitchell
    7:25 Mitchell talks about "experimenting around" with different instruments. He discusses the banjo and tunes it.
    9:45 [unidentified song, may be "Laid in His Grave"] Mitchell
    11:36 Mitchell retunes his banjo and introduces the next song.
    13:00 "Lord Randall" Mitchell
    15:10 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR051, Recorded: 1961-05-05, RXG 0738; 25:36
    This is the fourth of four parts of the Columbia Heights Boys Club 5th Annual Concert. No details of the concert are given. The recording quality is ok, but with an echo or distortion of some sort.
    Start Howie Mitchell introduces the next song.
    1:50 "Two Sisters" [also known as "Wind and Rain"] Mitchell, experimental mountain dulcimer
    3:50 Mitchell talks about the autoharp and introduces the next song.
    7:00 "Old Bangam" Mitchell
    10:00 Mitchell introduces the next song.
    10:40 [unidentified] Mitchell
    12:30 Mitchell tunes his banjo and introduces the next song.
    14:05 "Lady Gray" Mitchell, banjo
    17:40 Mitchell discusses the traditional mountain dulcimer.
    18:50 [unidentified instrumental] Mitchell, dulcimer
    19:40 "Old Lady and the Pig" Mitchell, dulcimer
    22:33 Mitchell introduces the last song of the set and tunes the dulcimer.
    23:10 "Drink to Me Only With Thine Eyes" Mitchell, dulcimer
    25:36 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR052 Part 1 of 2, Recorded: 1961-12-12, RXG 0739; 52:31
    This tape appears to be the first of two parts of a concert by Peggy Seeger. There is a folder in the collection for this SR. Notes in the folder state that the venue is Graham Chapel, Washington University, St, Louis, MO.
    Start "When First Unto This Country" Peggy Seeger [vocal and autoharp]
    3:38 Seeger talks about the songs she sings. She introduces the next song.
    4:37 [unidentified song, perhaps "Pretty Saro"] Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    7:57 Seeger talks about people's reactions to concerts and people singing at concerts.
    8:48 "Yes, Ma'am" Seeger [vocal and guitar]
    10:27 Seeger talks about folk music and popular music.
    11:40 "Freight Train" Seeger [vocal and guitar]
    14:07 Seeger talks about a game she played when she was a young girl.
    15:30 "I'll Not Marry a Man That's Rich" [also known as "I'll Not Marry At All"] Seeger [a cappella]
    17:20 Seeger talks about women's independence of mind.
    18:15 "Lady Margaret" Seeger [vocal and autoharp]
    24:18 "Seeger talks about American and British folk songs. She introduces the next song.
    26:35 [unidentified song, may be called "Charlie"] Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    28:49 "Derby Ram" Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    31:27 "It's a Lie" [sailor' version of "Derby Ram"] Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    33:05 Seeger Talks about how folk songs change. She introduces the next song.
    34:05 "John Riley" [version 1] Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    37:40 Seeger talks about another version of the song.
    38:01 "John Riley" [version 2] Seeger [vocal and autoharp]
    41:35 Seeger talks about folks songs being used in teaching school in England. She introduces the next song.
    43:20 "Five Times Five" Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    47:00 "Gypsy Davey" Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    49:35 "The Maid on the shore" Seeger [a cappella]
    52:31 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR052 Part 2 of 2, Recorded: 1961-12-12, RXG 0739; 50:22
    This tape appears to be the second part of a concert by Peggy Seeger. There is a folder in the collection for this SR. Notes in the folder state that the venue is Graham Chapel, Washington University, St, Louis, MO. Tacked on to the very end of the tape, starting at 48:45, is a recording of the Dillard Brothers.
    Start Seeger talks about a song being complete.
    0:45 Seeger performs several short, "compete" songs including: "Old Kate She Baked a Cake," "Lula Gal," "Cross Eyed Gopher," "The Old Cow Dies," Hick, Hike, Hoke," and "The Spanish Cavalier" Seeger [vocal and guitar]
    3:45 Seeger introduces the next song.
    4:05 "When I was a Little Girl" Seeger [vocal and guitar]
    4:47 Unidentified song. [The collection notes say it is "All alone and Lonely"] Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    7:55 Seeger introduces the next song.
    8:55 "Green Wood Sidey" Seeger [a cappella]
    11:30 Seeger introduces the next song.
    13:18 "The Three Welshman [sic]" Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    18:15 Seeger introduces the next song.
    19:08 "Four Marys" [also known as "Mary Hamilton"] Seeger [vocal and guitar]
    22:33 Seeger discusses the previous song and introduces the next song.
    24:13 "I Am a Girl of Constant Sorrow" Seeger [vocal and guitar]
    27:30 Seeger says she will do three songs recently written in Britain.
    28:42 Title not given. Seeger [vocal and guitar] [This is a lament for a school boy killed in an accident.]
    32:30 Seeger says the next song is about an incident which was a protest response to dramatic raise of rents in London.
    35:07 "The Landlord's Nine Questions" Seeger [vocal and banjo]
    39:23 Seeger says this next song is about a protest to the amount of strontium 90 in the air in England.
    41:15 No title given Seeger [vocal and guitar]
    44:02 Seeger introduces the next song. She says it is a Christmas song.
    44:50 "If anybody Asks You Who I Am" Seeger [vocal and guitar]
    48:33 End of the Peggy Seeger concert.
    48:45 "Banjo in the Hollow" The Dillard's [Doug and Rodney] [There is a folder in the collection for this SR. Notes in the folder state that this was recorded "in the Hollow, 7/1/62, St, Louis, MO.]
    50:22 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR053, Recorded: 1961-12-17, RAA 54529; 52:53
    This is a recording for a John Dildine radio broadcast from (probably) December 17, 1961. He plays recordings of Judy Collins, Tommy Makem and the Clancy Brothers, and Ed McCurdy
    Start "Railroad Bill" the opening theme song. He introduces tonight's program.
    2:24 "Pretty Saro" Collins
    5:30 Dildine talks about the previous song and introduces the next song.
    5:55 "John Riley" Collins
    9:27 Dildine says that on "John Riley" the second guitar was played by Fred
    Hellerman and the banjo was played by Eric Darling. Dildine does a commercial
    for the Showboat Lounge. He introduces the next recording.
    11:45 Tommy Makem introduces Peter Seeger and Bruce Langhorn.
    12:00 ‘The whistling Gypsy" Makem, lead vocal
    15:50 "Johnny Lad" Pat Clancy, lead vocal
    17:34 Dildine talks about the next song.
    18:04 "The Old Orange Flute" Makem, lead vocal
    21:43 "Brennan on the Moor" vocal, all
    23:42 Dildine discusses the record he's been playing. He does a station break. He introduces the recordings of Ed McCurdy.
    25:15 "Gypsy Davie" McCurdy
    27:20 Dildine talks about the previous song and introduces the next song.
    27:48 "Hunters of Kentucky" McCurdy
    30:43 Dildine talks about the previous song and introduces the next song.
    31:55 "Rock About My Pretty Saro" McCurdy
    34:04 Dildine introduces the next song.
    34:50 "My Pretty Little Pink" McCurdy
    36:01 Dildine introduces the next two hymns.
    36:23 "Simple gifts" [A Shaker song from 1848] McCurdy, a cappella